(Howard:)I mean, even Donkey Kong
had Donkey Kong Jr.
(Howard:)So he could teach someone
how to kidnap princesses...
(Howard:)...and throw barrels
at Italian plumbers.
(Leonard:)You know, there's no guarantee even if
you have kids you're gonna like them.
(Raj:)Wow, that's rough.
Where'd you get that?
(Leonard:)It's right off the dust jacket
of my mom's last book.
(Howard:)Maybe me and Bernadette
aren't right for each other.
(Leonard:)Look, Howard, I'd say
there's a lot of fish in the sea...
(Leonard:)...but I watched you dangle your hook
for years.
(Leonard:)Do not throw her back.
(Bernadette:)I don't want to,
but this is kind of a deal breaker.
What will your mom say
if you call off the wedding?
Heh, it'll kill her.
If I don't give her grandchildren...
(Howard:)...that'll kill her too. So either way
on the Mom front, I'm golden.